saveup.com 2013-08-06

# SaveUp | Privacy Policy

## **Privacy** policy.

SaveUp, Inc. ("SaveUp") is committed to protecting your privacy. We have prepared this Privacy Policy to describe to you our practices regarding the Personal Data (as defined below) we collect from users of our website, located at saveup.com ("Site") and the services made available through the Site ("Services"). Capitalized terms not defined in this Privacy Policy have the meaning set forth in the Terms of Service. 

##### User Consent

By submitting Personal Data through our Site or Services, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and you expressly consent to the processing of your Personal Data in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

##### A Note About Children

We do not intentionally gather Personal Data about visitors who are under the age of 13. 

##### Types of Data We Collect

SaveUp collects Personal Data and Anonymous Data from you when you visit our Site, when you send us information or communications, and/or when you use the Services. "Personal Data" means data that allows someone to identify or contact you, including, for example, your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, as well as any other non-public information about you that is associated with or linked to any of the foregoing data. Personal Data includes your FI Access Information and FI Account Data. "Anonymous Data" means data that is not associated with or linked to your Personal Data; Anonymous Data does not permit the identification of individual persons. We collect Personal Data and Anonymous Data, as described below. 

##### Personal Data You Provide to Us

We collect Personal Data from you, such as your e-mail address, when you register for an account to log in to the Services. 

In order for you to benefit from the full functionality of our Services, you must also provide your FI Access Information to allow us to access your FI Account Data at third party Financial Institutions for use by the Services. 

We also retain information on your behalf, such as FI Account Data for the Financial Institutions for which you have provided your FI Access Information. 

If you provide us feedback or contact us via e-mail (e.g., in response to an employment opportunity posted on our website), we will collect your name and e-mail address, as well as any other content included in the e-mail, in order to send you a reply, and any information that you submit to us, such as a resume. 

When you participate in one of our surveys or sweepstakes, we may collect additional profile information. 

When you post messages on the forums or message boards of our Site, the information contained in your posting will be stored on our servers and other users will be able to see it. 

We also collect other types of Personal Data that you provide to us voluntarily, such as first name, last name, mailing address, phone number, salary, age, date of birth, gender, education level, and marital status. 

We may also collect Personal Data, such as demographic information from you via the Services or at other points in our Site that state that Personal Data is being collected. 

You may choose not to provide us with certain information, but this may limit the features that you can use or the functionality of the Services. 

##### Personal Data Collected via Technology

To make our Site and Services more useful to you, our servers (which may be hosted by a third party service provider) collect Personal Data from you, including internet protocol address, geographic location, operating system, browser type, domain name, and a date/time stamp for your visit. Like most Internet services, we automatically gather this Personal Data and store it in log files each time you visit the Site or access your account on the Services. 

**"Cookies"** are small pieces of information that a website sends to your computer’s hard drive while you are viewing a web site. We use Cookies and navigational data like Uniform Resource Locators (URL) to gather information regarding the date and time of your visit and the solutions and information for which you searched and which you viewed. 

**"Web Beacons"** are images embedded in a Web page or email to measure and analyze site usage and activity. We, or third party providers acting on our behalf, may use Web Beacons to help us analyze Site usage and to improve the Services. 

**Personal Data That We Collect from You About Others.** If you decide to invite a third party to use the Services, we will collect such third party’s name and e-mail address so that we may send such third party an invitation to use the Services. You or the third party may contact us at customerservice@saveup.com to request the removal of this information from our database. 

**Personal and/or Anonymous Data Collected by Third Parties.** We may receive Personal and/or Anonymous Data about you from other sources like telephone or fax, or from companies that offer their products and/or services on the Site ("Third Party Companies"). We may add this information to the information we have already collected from you via the Site in order to improve the Services. 

**Data Aggregation.** In order for you to benefit from the full functionality of our Services, our Services require access to your FI Account Data. We use a third party service provider to facilitate the aggregation of your FI Account Data from your Financial Institutions, including, but not limited to, storing your FI Access Information, accessing your FI Account Data, and retrieving your FI Account Data from such third party financial institutions. Except for your FI Account Data, SaveUp does not retain any information related to your account with your Financial Institutions, including, but not limited to, your FI Account Information, however, for your convenience, our third party service provider may retain FI Access Information in order for the Services to receive updates to your FI Account Data. 

##### Use of Your Data

**General Use.** In general, Personal Data you submit to us is used either to respond to requests that you make, or to aid us in serving you better. SaveUp uses your Personal Data in the following ways: 

  * to provide you with the Services;
  * to analyze your personal finance activities and reward you with credits for your performance of certain activities;
  * to personalize and better tailor the features, performance and support of the Services for your use;
  * to send you administrative notifications, such as security or support and maintenance advisories;
  * to respond to your inquiries related to employment opportunities or other requests;
  * to send you promotional/marketing information, newsletters, surveys, offers or other information;
  * to provide you with opportunities and functionality that we think would be of particular interest to you;
  * to improve the quality of the Site and the Services,
  * to analyze, benchmark and conduct research on, user data and user interactions with the Services; and
  * to conduct market research, planning, troubleshooting, planning problems, detecting and protecting against error, fraud, or other criminal activity;
  * to solicit your feedback.

**Cookies.** We may use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them) to provide you with a more personal and interactive experience on the Site, to tailor the Site to your interests, to better understand how you interact with the Services, and to monitor aggregate usage and web traffic routing on the Site and Services. We may use third party service providers to help us analyze certain online activities. For example, these service providers may help us analyze visitor activity on the Site. We may allow these service providers to use Cookies or other technologies to perform these services for us. We do not share any Personal Data about our customers with these third party service providers, and these service providers do not collect Personal Data on our behalf. Persistent Cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. If you choose to disable Cookies, some areas of the Site may not work properly. 

**Ad Networks and Third Party Cookies.** We may have agreements with companies that serve advertising on the Services on behalf of third parties ("Ad Networks"). These Ad Networks may place or recognize a unique Cookie on your browser. Ad Networks use Cookies to understand Web usage patterns of people who see advertisements, to control the sequence of advertisements you see, to provide you with the most relevant advertising, and to make sure you don't see the same ad too many times. Ad Networks may connect information about pages you visit through our Services with information about pages you visit on other sites and show you advertising based on this combined information. We do not control Ad Networks or what they do with the information they collect. Many Ad Networks participate in the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) and abide by NAI principles, which prohibit members from connecting Personal Information to information they collect through cookies without your explicit consent. If you would like more information and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, go to www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp. 

**Creation of Anonymous Data.** We may create Anonymous Data records from Personal Data by excluding information (such as your name) that make the data personally identifiable to you. We use this Anonymous Data to analyze request and usage patterns so that we may enhance the content of the Site or the Services and improve site navigation. SaveUp reserves the right to use and disclose Anonymous Data to Third Party Companies in its discretion. 

**Feedback.** If you provide feedback on the Site or the Services to us, we may use such feedback for any purpose, provided we will not associate such feedback with your Personal Data. SaveUp will collect any information contained in such communication and will treat the Personal Data in such communication in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

##### Disclosure of Your Personal Data

**Affiliates.** Although we currently do not have a parent SaveUp, any subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under a common control (collectively, "Affiliates"), we may in the future. We may share some or all of your Personal Data with these Affiliates, in which case we will require our Affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy. If another SaveUp acquires SaveUp or our assets, that SaveUp will possess the Personal Data collected by it and us and will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Data as described in this Privacy Policy. 

**Forums, Message Boards and Chats.** We may make message boards, chat rooms, and other interactive forums available on the Services. You should be aware that any information which you post to these interactive forums or otherwise choose to make publicly available, including your Personal Data, may be disclosed and available to all users who have access to that portion of the Services, and is therefore no longer private. By using these interactive forums, you agree that we are not responsible for any information that you disclose or communicate in such forums, and any disclosures you make are at your own risk. Please be thoughtful about what you post and make publicly available through the Services. 

**Other Disclosures.** Regardless of any choices you make regarding your Personal Data (as described below), SaveUp may disclose Personal Data if it believes in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to (a) comply with relevant laws or to respond to subpoenas or warrants served on SaveUp or (b) protect or defend the rights or property of SaveUp or other users of the Services. 

##### Third Parties

**Links to Third Party Websites.** The Services may link to websites operated by third parties that we do not control. This includes any sites that you linked to from advertisements that appear on the Services. Our provision of such links is for your convenience and does not signify our endorsement of such other website or location or its products, services, or contents. When you click on such a link, you will leave our site and go to another site. During this process, another entity may collect Personal Data or Anonymous Data from you. We have no control over, do not review, and cannot be responsible for, these outside websites or their products, services, or content. Please be aware that the terms of this Privacy Policy do not apply to these outside websites, or to any collection of data after you click on links to such outside websites. 

**Disclosure to Third Party Service Providers.** Except as otherwise stated in this policy, we do not generally sell, trade, share, or rent the Personal Data collected from the Services to other entities. However, we may employ, and share your Personal Data with, third party companies and individuals ("Service Providers") to facilitate or enhance our Site or Services, to provide the Services on our behalf, to perform tasks (e.g., without limitation, maintenance services, database management, web analytics and improvement of the Site or Services), to retrieve and store FI Access Information and FI Account Data, or to assist us in analyzing how our Services are used. These third party service providers are required not to use or disclose your Personal Data other than to provide the services requested by us. You expressly consent to the sharing of your Personal Data with our Service Providers for the sole purpose of providing services requested by us. 

**Disclosure to Third Party Companies.** We may enter into agreements with Third Party Companies. A Third Party SaveUp may want access to Personal Data that we collect from its customers. As a result, we may disclose your Personal Data to a Third Party Company; however, we will not disclose your Personal Data to Third Party Companies for the Third Party Companies’ own direct marketing purposes, unless you have "opted-in" by following the instructions we provide to allow such disclosure. If you have opted-in to receive e-mail communications from a Third Party Company and later wish to discontinue receipt of these e-mails, please contact the Third Party Company directly to update your preferences. The privacy policies of our Third Party Companies may apply to the use and disclosure of your Personal Data that we collect and disclose to such Third Party Companies. Because we do not control the privacy practices of our Third Party Companies, you should read and understand their privacy policies. 

**Compensation Disclaimer** Please note that SaveUp has financial relationships with some of the merchants mentioned here. SaveUp may be compensated if consumers choose to utilize the links located throughout the content on this site and generate sales for the said merchant. 

##### Your Choices Regarding Your Personal Data

**Choices.** We offer you choices regarding the collection, use, and sharing of your Personal Data. We may periodically send you newsletters or messages via e-mail, telephone, postal mail, SMS, or social networks that notify you of new credits, prizes, winnings, or opportunities available through the Site or Services, provide you with updates regarding the Site or Services, and directly promote the use of the Site or Services and may contain advertisements for Third Party Companies. When you receive newsletters or promotional communications from us, you may indicate a preference to stop receiving further communications from us and you will have the opportunity to "opt-out" by contacting us directly (please see contact information below). Should you decide to opt-out of receiving future communications, we may share your contact information with third parties to ensure that you do not receive further communications from third parties. Despite your indicated preferences, we may send you notices of any updates to our Terms of Service or Privacy Policy. 

**Changes to Personal Data.** You may change any of your Personal Data in your account by editing your profile within the Services. You may request deletion of your Personal Data by us, but please note that we may be required (by law or otherwise) to keep this information and not delete it (or to keep this information for a certain time, in which case we will comply with your deletion request only after we have fulfilled such requirements). When we delete any information, it will be deleted from the active database, but may remain in our archives. 

##### Security of Your Personal Data

SaveUp is committed to protecting the security of your Personal Data. We use a variety of industry-standard physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to help protect your Personal Data from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. We also require you to enter a password to access your account information. Please do not disclose your account password to unauthorized people. From the time you submit your username and password, communications between your computer and the SaveUp are encrypted using secure socket layer technology to make your information unreadable as it passes over the Internet. While the SaveUp uses these and other reasonable efforts to protect your Personal Data, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, SaveUp cannot guarantee absolute security of your Personal Data. 

##### Contact Information

SaveUp welcomes your comments or questions regarding this Privacy Policy. Please e-mail us at customerservice@saveup.com or contact us at the following address: 

SaveUp, Inc.   
Attn: Customer Service   
480 2nd Street, Suite 202   
San Francisco CA 94107 

##### Dispute Resolution

If you believe that SaveUp has not adhered to this Statement, please contact SaveUp by email at customerservice@saveup.com. We will do our best to address your concerns. If you feel that your complaint has been addressed incompletely, we invite you to let us know for further investigation. 

##### Changes to This Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is subject to occasional revision, and if we make any substantial changes in the way we use your Personal Data, we will notify you by sending you an e-mail to the last e-mail address you provided to us and/or by prominently posting notice of the changes on our website. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be effective immediately if you are a new user of the Services and will be effective thirty (30) calendar days after posting of notice of such changes on the Site if you are an existing user, provided that, if you are an existing user, any material changes shall be effective for you upon the earlier of thirty (30) calendar days following posting of notice of such changes on the Site or thirty (30) calendar days after dispatch of an e-mail notice of such changes to you. Please note that at all times you are responsible for updating your Personal Data to provide us with your most current e-mail address. In the event that the last e-mail address that you have provided us is not valid, or for any reason is not capable of delivering to you the notice described above, our dispatch of the e-mail containing such notice will nonetheless constitute effective notice of the changes described in the notice. In any event, changes to this Privacy Policy may affect our use of Personal Data that you provided to us prior to our notification to you of the changes. If you do not wish to permit changes in our use of your Personal Data, you must notify us prior to the effective date of the changes that you wish to deactivate your account with us. Continued use of the Site or Services, following notice of such changes shall indicate your acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes. 

This Privacy Policy was last revised on July 19, 2011.
